zaption.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Zaption

## Last Updated: August 3rd, 2015

This privacy policy sets out how Zaption, its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, the "Company") uses and protects any information that you give Company when you use this website. Company is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Company may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

**Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect from Registered Users**

We may collect the following personally identifiable information ("PII") if you become a registered user: 

  * name 
  * email address 

**Passive Collection of Non-Personal Information**

The Company's website often requires the use of encrypted or non-encrypted cookies. Cookies are data that a web server transfers to an individual's computer for recordkeeping purposes. Cookies are an industry standard used by most websites and help facilitate users' ongoing access to and use of a particular website, for example by providing information used to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. 

Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the website that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

As part of the login process, the Company's website may use persistent cookies when you give us permission to do so. Persistent cookies are cookies stored on your computer. They allow us, with your permission, to remember information about you, such as your log-in information, so that we may enhance your experience the next time you visit the Company's website. You must give your permission to allow the Company's website to set persistent cookies. You may opt-out of the use of persistent cookies at any time. 

We may also use flash cookies, also known as "local shared objects," on the Company's website during the login process. Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies and are used to remember the website settings in order to personalize the look and feel of the website. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Please note, however, that declining cookies may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Company's website and/or Software as a Service ("SaaS"). 

Other passive and non-personal information we may gather include the "IP address" of your device on the network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you. We may also gather the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed the Company's website, the type of web browsers and operating system or platform used, the names of the pages you visit while at the Company's website, what videos you watch and any other interaction you have with the Company's website or SaaS. 

**What we do with the information we gather**

The Company will not disclose your PII, or passive, non-personal information to third-parties. We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 
  * We may use the information for internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information, which we think you may find interesting using the email address, which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail. 

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information, which you provide whilst visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties, which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information, which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

The Company offers accounts for no charge. As a result, even if you were a paying customer at one time and became a non-payer customer, the Company will continue to maintain your Account and your UGC. As a result, your PII, your passive information associated with your PII, and your UGC will be maintained by the Company indefinitely. If you would like your PII permanently deleted you need to first "deactivate" your Zaption account and then send an email to [support@zaption.com](mailto:support@zaption.com) to specifically request the deletion of your PII. You may deactivate your account by logging into Zaption with your Registered Account, selecting your Account settings, selecting "Deactivate My Account," and confirm your selection. Upon Account deactivation you will lose access to all your UGC content and account information. In order to restore access to your Account and your UGC, you simply need to log back into Zaption with your previous Account and password. Note: individual user accounts associated with an Institutional User (such as a school, university, organization) may not have the permission to deactivate their own accounts. If no deactivation option is visible, please contact the administrator for your organization for assistance. 

To contact the Company about any privacy matters, send an e-mail to [support@zaption.com](mailto:support@zaption.com) or call 415-997-9979
